in this video we're going to look at
在这个视频中，我们将要看
creating and running automated tests in
在以下环境中创建和运行自动化测试
IntelliJ IDEA and how to get coverage
IntelliJ IDEA以及如何获得报道
information for your tests IntelliJ IDEA
测试信息IntelliJ IDEA
aims to make it as easy as possible to
旨在使它尽可能容易
navigate to or create tests so if I try
导航到或创建测试，以便我尝试
to navigate to the test for a production
导航到生产测试
class and the IDE can't find one it will
类，IDE找不到它
ask you if you want to create it by
询问您是否要创建它
default you have several options for the
默认情况下，您有几个选项
type of tests to create we're going to
要创建的测试类型
use J and 4 as this is still the most
使用J和4，因为这仍然是最多的
common framework for Java unit tests you
Java单元测试的通用框架
can of course change the name of the
当然可以更改名称
test if you wish and there are options
测试您是否愿意，是否有选择
for generating setup and teardown
用于生成设置和拆卸
methods all tests for the methods in the
方法中的所有测试
class you're testing but we're going to
您正在测试的课程，但我们要
start with an empty test class you can
从一个空的测试类开始
generate a new test method using command
使用命令生成新的测试方法
N or alt an insert for Windows and Linux
N或alt Windows和Linux的插入
IntelliJ IDEA makes it easy for you to
IntelliJ IDEA使您轻松实现
sketch out the tests you want to write
勾勒出您要编写的测试
offering the usual code completion and
提供通常的代码完成和
suggestions when you're ready to run the
准备运行时的建议
tests you can do this a number of
测试您可以这样做
different ways which will show
将显示的不同方式
throughout this video the first and
在整个视频中，第一个和
probably easiest approach is to use the
可能最简单的方法是使用
gutter icon on the test method to run it
测试方法上的装订线图标以运行它
our test fails as we expected since we
我们的测试失败了
haven't implemented the functionality
尚未实现功能
yet IntelliJ IDEA shows you the failure
但是IntelliJ IDEA向您显示了失败
why it failed and offers a detailed
为什么失败，并提供详细
comparison between actual and expected
实际与预期之间的比较
values which is very useful for more
值对于更多有用
complex values such as JSON or complex
复杂值，例如JSON或complex
domain objects we can navigate back to
我们可以导航到的域对象
our implementation to make the simplest
我们的实现使最简单
fix for our test and this time we'll use
修复测试，这次我们将使用
the run icon in the navigation bar to
导航栏中的运行图标
run the test again
再次运行测试
now it passes so everything goes green
现在它过去了，所以一切都变成绿色
this time when we choose to navigate to
这次，当我们选择导航到
the test IntelliJ IDEA locates our new
测试IntelliJ IDEA找到了我们的新产品
test class and we can jump straight to
测试课，我们可以直接跳到
it IntelliJ IDEA makes it very
IntelliJ IDEA使其非常
straightforward to develop Ana
直接开发Ana
test-driven development way for example
以测试驱动的开发方式为例
now I'm going to create another test to
现在我要创建另一个测试
identify further functionality for my
确定我的其他功能
analyze mood method this time I'll use
这次我将使用情绪分析方法
the keyboard shortcut shift ctrl R on
键盘快捷键Shift Ctrl R开启
the Mac or shift ctrl f10 on Windows and
Mac或Windows上的shift ctrl f10和
Linux to run my new method to get back
Linux运行我的新方法取回
to the production code from the test we
到测试中的生产代码
use the same shortcut as getting to the
使用与进入相同的快捷方式
test from the code shift command T or
从代码移位命令T或
shift ctrl T on Windows and Linux
在Windows和Linux上移动ctrl T
mastering these shortcuts will
掌握这些快捷方式将
significantly speed up coding and
大大加快了编码速度，
testing now we're in the production code
现在测试我们在生产代码中
we can make the simplest changes that
我们可以进行最简单的更改
were satisfied both tests
对两个测试都满意
when this is done we can rerun the last
完成后，我们可以重新运行最后一个
test with ctrl f5 and we should see this
用ctrl f5测试，我们应该看到这个
turn green as well fixing problems isn't
变绿以及修复问题不是
always as easy so let's go back to our
总是那么容易，所以让我们回到我们的
test class where we have another new
测试班，我们还有另一个新的
test method the gutter icons in the test
测试方法测试中的装订线图标
class show a green circle next to tests
班级在测试旁边显示一个绿色圆圈
that have been run and passed and our
已经运行并通过的
new test just has the green one icon
新测试只有一个绿色的图标
when we run all the tests in this class
当我们运行此类中的所有测试时
using the class level gutter icon we can
使用班级装订线图标，我们可以
see our new test fails clicking on the
看到我们的新测试失败，请点击
failing test brings it into the editor
测试失败将其带入编辑器
if we don't know why this test failed we
如果我们不知道为什么这个测试失败了，我们
could put a breakpoint in the production
可能在生产中设置断点
code and then we can choose to debug
代码，然后我们可以选择调试
just the failing test by right-clicking
右键单击只是失败的测试
on it in the run window I can even put
在运行窗口中，我什至可以放
breakpoints on lambda expressions in my
我的lambda表达式的断点
stream operations and then step through
流操作，然后逐步执行
to see what the problem might be
看看可能是什么问题
when I think I've solved the problem I
当我认为我已经解决了问题时
can rerun the test as normal
可以照常重新运行测试
there are a number of options and
有很多选择，
settings to run tests in IntelliJ IDEA
设置以在IntelliJ IDEA中运行测试
so to demonstrate these I'm running all
为了演示这些，我将全部运行
the tests in a real application by
实际应用中的测试
default the IDE will show you the set of
默认情况下，IDE将向您显示一组
all tests that have been run as these
像这样运行的所有测试
tests pass you see the green icons and
测试通过，您会看到绿色图标，并且
the test names in the run window
运行窗口中的测试名称
since we're probably more interested in
因为我们可能更感兴趣
failures than successes you can choose
您可以选择失败胜于成功
to hide tests that passed similarly you
隐藏同样通过的测试
can hide ignored or disable tests if you
可以隐藏被忽略或禁用测试，如果您
choose you can sort the tests
选择您可以对测试进行排序
alphabetically rather than have them in
而不是按字母顺序
the order they were found and you can
找到它们的顺序，您可以
expand to see all the individual test
展开以查看所有单个测试
methods or contract to hide the detail
隐藏细节的方法或合同
the run window shows a lot of
运行窗口显示很多
information about the status of the
有关状态的信息
running tests like how many have run how
运行测试，例如有多少运行方式
many there are in total how many have
总共有多少个
been ignored and how many fail and the
被忽略，有多少失败，
progress bar gives you an idea of how
进度栏可让您了解
much longer the tests will take and it
测试将花费更长的时间，
will turn from green to red if a single
如果单个，则将从绿色变为红色
test fails track running tests forces
测试失败跟踪运行测试力
the window to show every test as it runs
显示每个测试运行的窗口
and lets you follow the progress of the
并让您追踪进度
tests you could turn off inline
测试您可以内联关闭
statistics which will hide the time it
统计信息将隐藏时间
took to run each test there are numerous
进行每项测试的人很多
other settings you can experiment with
您可以尝试的其他设置
in order to have the run window show the
为了使运行窗口显示
information to you in the most useful
最有用的信息给您
way for example you can have the window
例如，您可以拥有窗户
jump to the first failing test when all
全部跳到第一个失败的测试
the tests are finished so you can fix
测试完成，因此您可以修复
any problems immediately
任何问题立即
now let's look at test coverage it's
现在让我们看看测试范围
great to have a series of tests that
进行一系列测试很高兴
pass but it can be more useful to
通过，但是对
understand which areas of your code are
了解代码的哪些区域
covered by these tests and more
这些测试及更多内容
importantly which code is not covered by
重要的是，哪些代码不属于
tests this time when we run all our
这次当我们运行所有的时候进行测试
tests we select run all tests with
我们选择的测试运行所有测试
coverage by default this will use the
默认情况下，它将使用
IntelliJ IDEA coverage tool but you can
IntelliJ IDEA覆盖工具，但您可以
select other tools like jacoco in the
选择其他工具，例如jacoco
settings when all the tests are run the
运行所有测试时的设置
coverage window shows a breakdown of the
覆盖范围窗口显示了
coverage by package if we navigate to
如果我们导航到包，则按包覆盖
the main package of our application we
我们应用程序的主要包
can see which classes are well covered
可以看到哪些课程涵盖得很好
by tests and which might need more
通过测试，可能还需要更多
thorough testing this information is
彻底测试此信息是
also available in the project window at
也可以在项目窗口中找到
the package and class level when we open
打开时的包和类级别
a class in the editor colors in the
编辑器中的类的颜色
gutter show the coverage level green for
装订线显示绿色的覆盖级别
high coverage red for low these colors
高覆盖红色，低这些颜色
can be configured which may be
可以配置
particularly useful if you're like me
如果你像我一样特别有用
and have problems distinguishing red and
并在区分红色和
green as with all IntelliJ IDEA windows
与所有IntelliJ IDEA窗口一样呈绿色
the coverage window has options for
覆盖范围窗口具有用于
customizing the display according to
根据以下内容定制显示
what you find most useful and you can
您发现最有用的东西
generate an HTML coverage report so if
生成HTML覆盖率报告，因此，如果
you do run your tests with coverage in
您确实在覆盖范围内运行测试
the IDE and want to show the results
IDE，并希望显示结果
with the rest of the team or external
与团队的其他成员或外部
parties you can share this report and it
各方，您可以共享此报告及其
contains all the same information we
包含我们所有相同的信息
just saw including colors on the source
刚刚看到包括来源上的颜色
code to indicate good and poor test
表示测试的好坏的代码
coverage these testing features aren't
没有涵盖这些测试功能
just for Java or j-unit right at the
仅适用于Java或j单元
beginning of the screencast you saw
您看到的截屏视频的开始
IntelliJ IDEA has support for multiple
IntelliJ IDEA支持多种
JVM testing frameworks including the
JVM测试框架包括
groovy framework Spock which you can see
您可以看到的groovy框架Spock
here many of the features we've shown in
这里我们展示了许多功能
this video are available in these other
这部影片可在其他影片中找到
frameworks and even for testing in other
框架，甚至用于其他测试
languages like JavaScript in this video
该视频中的JavaScript之类的语言
you saw how to create run rerun and
您看到了如何创建运行重新运行以及
debug tests as well as being able to see
调试测试以及能够看到
the coverage of your automated tests
自动化测试的范围
thanks for watching
谢谢收看